ILR School 40th Anniversary Audio cassettes /4078 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School 40th Anniversary Audio cassettes
1986
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4078 AV
1.33 cubic feet
1.3 linear ft.
Audiovisual materials.
Audio recordings from the celebration of the 40th anniversary of the ILR school
8595142
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 05, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 27, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4078: ILR School 40th Anniversary Documents /4078 MB: ILR School 40th Anniversary Memorabilia /4104 OHT: ILR School 40th Anniversary Interviews
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8595142
- 40th Anniv. Sat. May 3, 1986 - Luncheon Speaker Douglas Fraser UAW (Box 1)
- 40th Anniv. Sat., May 3, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 2 pm (Box 2)
- 40th Anniv. Friday, May 2, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 2 pm (Box 3)
- 40th Anniv. Friday May 2, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 2 pm (Box 4)
- 40th Anniv. Saturday May 3, 1986 - Room 110 Ives - 11 am (Box 5)
- 40th Anniv. Sat., May 3, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 10:30 am (Box 6)
- 40th Anniv. Saturday, May 3, 1986 - Room 120 Ives, - 2 pm (Box 7)
- 40th Anniv. Saturday, May 3, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 9 am (Box 8)
- 40th Anniv. Saturday, May 3, 1986 - Room 120 Ives - 9 am (Box 9)
- 40th Anniv. Sat., May 3, 1986 - Dinner Presentations Risley (Box 10)
- 40th Anniv. Friday, May 2, 1986 - Dinner Speaker - Stephen Schlossberg, Dept. of Labor (Box 11)
- 40th Anniv. Saturday, May 3, 1986 - Dinner Presentations Risley (Box 12)